Johnny Science Papers 1948-2000 (Bulk 1988-1998) MSS.268
Fales Library and Special Collections
- Series I: Projects, 220132
  - Science: "Textbook Images & Text", c1980; 221209 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - [Science/VON LMO Max's Kansas City Flyers], c1980; 221212 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - "Science with Roland Alphonso at Max's Kansas City" [Flyer Mock-Up], 1980; 221210 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - [Science Zine], c1980; 221213 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - "The Second Coming Out: A Self Help Guide for Heavy Set Gay Men" [Survey], undated; 221214 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - "Secret Occult Info Revealed!" [Flyers], undated; 221215 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - [Sex Cards / My Personal Ad" [Flyers, Notes], 1990 - 1995; 221216 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Sex Catalog: Products for Men, 4/20/99; 221217 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - [S/M: Clippings, Flyers], 1990s; 221220 (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - "S/M Comic Book" [Illustrations by Johnny Science], various; 221221 (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - [S/M: "Dangerous Top" Research], 1996; 221222 (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - "The Sneaky Little Sadist" [Premise by Johnny Science], undated; 221235 (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - "Speech at the 11th Annual L/G/B Pride Rally" by Bet Power, May 9, 1992; 221240 (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - The SS: The Third Reich [Time Life Book], 1988; 221252 (Box 5, Folder 19)
  - [St. Anthony: Religious Flyers, Pamphlets], various; 221254 (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - [Stewart, Patrick - Clippings], various; 221260 (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - Straight to Hell: The Manhattan Review of Unnatural Acts - Number 54, c1982; 221255 (Box 5, Folder 17)
  - Strange Motorcycle Gangs: Cycle Outlaws - Special Issue Volume 1, Number 1, undated; 221256 (Box 5, Folder 18)
  - "Swipe File" [Loose Clippings, Images], undated; 221257 (Box 5, Folder 19)
  - "Teddy Bare" [Flyers, Mock-Ups], undated; 221259 (Box 5, Folder 20)
  - "Teddy Bear, Inc." [Letterhead, Notes], 1995; 221258 (Box 5, Folder 21)
  - [Theater: Clippings], various; 221261 (Box 5, Folder 22)
  - [Theater: Flyers], 1990s; 221262 (Box 5, Folder 23)
  - [Tom of Finland: Clippings], 1996 - 1997; 221263 (Box 5, Folder 24)
  - The Underground: An Erotic Emporium, Inc. [Catalog], undated; 221264 (Box 5, Folder 25)
  - The Urban Herbalist - Number 11 [Zine], May 1994; 221265 (Box 5, Folder 26)
  - Ursus Major - Volume 1 Number 1, Volume 1 [Newsletters], Winter 1996, May 1997; 221266 (Box 5, Folder 27)
  - "The Valuable Intrinsic Worth of Individuality" by Johnny Science, undated; 221269 (Box 5, Folder 28)
  - VICE: Art + Entertainment Magazine - 1st Annual Photography Issue, September 1995; 221272 (Box 5, Folder 29)
  - Wings Video Club - Catalog Number 6, undated; 221275 (Box 5, Folder 30)
- Series II: Correspondence, 220135
  - [Addressed to Dan Austen / Johnny Science], 1995 - 1999; 221315 (Box 5, Folder 31)
  - [Addressed to Suzy Greengras], 1971; 221317 (Box 5, Folder 32)
  - [Harley Davidson Notebook: Phone Messages], c1996; 221320 (Box 5, Folder 33)
  - [Phone Sex File], 1995 - 1997; 221324 (Box 5, Folder 34)
  - [Rachlin, Katherine "Kit"], 1988, 1994, 2010; 221330 (Box 5, Folder 35)
  - [Schwartz, Bill], various; 221331 (Box 5, Folder 36)
  - [Sohlberg, Eric Russell], various; 221332 (Box 5, Folder 37)
  - [Sprinkle, Annie], c1996; 221333 (Box 5, Folder 38)
  - [Subscriptions], various; 221334 (Box 5, Folder 39)
- Series III: Photography, 220136
  - [Drag King Club Photography 1], undated; 221340 (Box 5, Folder 40)
  - [Max's Kansas City Scrapbook Pages], 1970, 1978 - 1980; 221341 (Box 5, Folder 41)
  - [Mixed Scrapbook Pages], undated; 221342 (Box 5, Folder 42)
  - [Childhood & Young Adulthood - Contact Sheets, Negatives, Photographs], 1957 - 1980; 221344 (Box Binder 1)
  - [Drag King Club Photography 2], 1990 - 1995; 221346 (Box Binder 1)
  - "Linda / Les & Annie" Promotional Slides for Publication, 1989; 221345 (Box Binder 1)
  - [Mixed Personal Photography], c1998 - 1999; 221347 (Box Binder 1)
- Series IV: Objects, 220138
  - [Collection of Handmade Pins by Johnny Science], December 1982; 221964 (Box 6, Object ID: 268.2.0001)
  - [Collection of Buttons & Personal Items], undated; 221993 (Box 6, Object ID: 268.2.0002)
  - "Grow a Pecker" Toy, undated; 221996 (Box 6, Object ID: 268.2.0003)
  - Sony M-19V Microcassette-Corder, undated; 222521 (Box 11, Object ID: 268.2.0008)
- Series V: Video recordings, 220139
  Conditions Governing Access
  Video materials have not been preserved and are currently unavailable to researchers.
  - "1st Live Show, Annie Special", January 12, 1999; ID: 268.0001; 222045 (Box 9, Media ID: 268.0001)
    Currently unavailable until duplication occurs.
    Original format: VHS
  - "Betty Dodson with Johnny", undated; ID: 268.0002; 222046 (Box 9, Media ID: 268.0002)
  - "Bob & Mo Show", undated; ID: 268.0003; 222048 (Box 9, Media ID: 268.0003)
  - "Club Casanova '97", 1997; ID: 268.0004; 222049 (Box 9, Media ID: 268.0004)
  - "Drag King Club - New Show", November 18, 1993; ID: 268.0005; 222050 (Box 9, Media ID: 268.0005)
    Original format: Ampex 3/4" Tape
  - 1. "Drag King Show at Club Casanova, Meow Mix" 2. "Book Release Party for 'Female Masculinity' by Judith Halberstam", October 30 (no year); ID: 268.0006; 222051 (Box 9, Media ID: 268.0006)
  - "Drag Kings 9BP", November 7, 1991; ID: 268.0007; 222091 (Box 9, Media ID: 268.0007)
  - "Drag Kings on Joan Rivers & Geraldo", 1992; ID: 268.0008; 222108 (Box 9, Media ID: 268.0008)
  - "Drag King Club (That Show) - NY Times Rebuttal #2", November 17, 2001; ID: 268.0009; 222109 (Box 9, Media ID: 268.0009)
  - "Drag Kings on Donohue", 1998; ID: 268.0010; 222112 (Box 9, Media ID: 268.0010)
  - "Drag Kings at Maury Povich", October 20, 1999; ID: 268.0011; 222113 (Box 9, Media ID: 268.0011)
  - "F/M Sampler from Lou Sullivan", 1984 - 1986; ID: 268.0012; 222114 (Box 9, Media ID: 268.0012)
  - "He Was She Promo", 1989; ID: 268.0013; 222116 (Box 9, Media ID: 268.0013)
  - "Geraldo I Master, Mistress Ecstasy's Erotic Circus", August 31, 1997; ID: 268.0014; 222118 (Box 9, Media ID: 268.0014)
  - "Jerry Springer", July 16, 1999; ID: 268.0015; 222119 (Box 9, Media ID: 268.0015)
  - "Johnny Science & Elvis La Femme", November 13, 1998; ID: 268.0016; 222120 (Box 9, Media ID: 268.0016)
  - "JS Talking Head", June 1999, August 31, 1999; ID: 268.0017; 222123 (Box 9, Media ID: 268.0017)
    Original format: Mini DV
  - "JS Talking Head at Kit's / Dred at Phoenix", undated; ID: 268.0018; 222126 (Box 9, Media ID: 268.0018)
  - "Lauren Makeover Master Footage", January 12, 1998; ID: 268.0019; 222129 (Box 9, Media ID: 268.0019)
  - "Linda / Les & Annie: A Female-to-Male Transexual Love Story", 1989; ID: 268.0020; 222130 (Box 9, Media ID: 268.0020)
    Original format: DVD
  - "Linda / Les & Annie, Dred's Birthday", undated; ID: 268.0021; 222133 (Box 9, Media ID: 268.0021)
  - "Maury Povich: Macho Men Who Are Really Women", June 28 1999; ID: 268.0022; 222135 (Box 9, Media ID: 268.0022)
  - "Maury Povich DK Show #3", November 18, 1999; ID: 268.0023; 222136 (Box 9, Media ID: 268.0023)
  - "Meow Mix Benefit with Dred, Justin Case", undated; ID: 268.0024; 222139 (Box 9, Media ID: 268.0024)
  - "Mo in Express Studio (Mo Part I)", undated; ID: 268.0025; 222142 (Box 9, Media ID: 268.0025)
  - "New/Old Meow Mix = Club Casanova", March 26, 1999; ID: 268.0026; 222144 (Box 9, Media ID: 268.0026)
  - "Opening Night of Club Casanova - Michael Wakefield", March 31, 1996; ID: 268.0027; 222147 (Box 9, Media ID: 268.0027)
  - "Ricki Lake: Lives of T/S, Gender Science Show", undated; ID: 268.0028; 222149 (Box 9, Media ID: 268.0028)
  - "Simon: 8mm Tripod Camera Copy", undated; ID: 268.0029; 222150 (Box 9, Media ID: 268.0029)
  - "Springer: Hermaphrodite Talk Soup Clip", undated; ID: 268.0030; 222151 (Box 9, Media ID: 268.0030)
  - "Science / Max's / Von LMO / DK Misc - 1st Shoot at MNN", December 9, 1997; ID: 268.0031; 222152 (Box 9, Media ID: 268.0031)
    Original format: Hi8
  - "That Show with Johnny Science: Episode 1", 1998; ID: 268.0032; 222153 (Box 9, Media ID: 268.0032)
  - "That Show First Season Sampler", undated; ID: 268.0033; 222154 (Box 9, Media ID: 268.0033)
  - "That Show with Johnny Science #6", December 11(no year); ID: 268.0034; 222155 (Box 9, Media ID: 268.0034)
  - "That Show with Johnny Science - Lauren Hastings", October 23 (no year); ID: 268.0035; 222156 (Box 9, Media ID: 268.0035)
  - "That Show with Johnny Science 18", March 5 (no year); ID: 268.0036; 222157 (Box 9, Media ID: 268.0036)
  - "That Show with Johnny Science: #1 - 2", 1998; ID: 268.0037; 222158 (Box 9, Media ID: 268.0037)
- Series VI: Sound recordings, 220143
  Audio materials have not been preserved and are currently unavailable to researchers.
  - "Best of Both Worlds T = 67, Johnny Science", undated; ID: 268.0038; 222165 (Box 10, Media ID: 268.0038)
    Original format: 1/4" Tape
  - "Basement Rehearsal Blondes", undated; ID: 268.0039; 222218 (Box 10, Media ID: 268.0039)
    Original format: Audio Cassette
  - "Boys & Girls Music Co.", July 1, 1984; ID: 268.0040; 222219 (Box 10, Media ID: 268.0040)
  - "Bryan Ferry, Leonard & Suzy Singing", undated; ID: 268.0041; 222222 (Box 10, Media ID: 268.0041)
    File Plan
  - Commercial Recordings, various; 222348 (Box 11)
    This is a collection of 17 commercial and assorted recordings from Johnny Science's personal library.
  - "Francis the Great", July 24, 1975; ID: 268.0042; 222223 (Box 10, Media ID: 268.0042)
  - "Fred Jorio - Sexstravaganza Tribal Sextrax", 1989; ID: 268.0043; 222224 (Box 10, Media ID: 268.0043)
  - "1 )Fred's New Stuff; Fred Jorio: New Soul Songs; 2) "What a Man" S&P edit #2; "Montobi" Jorio (sextribe mix), September 1998; ID: 268.0091; 231284 (Box 10, Media ID: 268.0091)
  - "Howard Stern Aircheck", May 27, 1988; ID: 268.0044; 222225 (Box 10, Media ID: 268.0044)
  - "I Miss You Now", undated; ID: 268.0045; 222226 (Box 10, Media ID: 268.0045)
  - "Joelle, Suzy & Jeff Singing & The Glen Echo Tapes", undated; ID: 268.0046; 222235 (Box 10, Media ID: 268.0046)
  - Microcassettes, 1986; 222350 (Box 11)
    This is a collection of 22 microcassettes of assorted recordings from Johnny Science's personal library. They are housed in an annotated cigar box.
  - "New Beats One Through Six", June 1992; ID: 268.0047; 222236 (Box 10, Media ID: 268.0047)
  - "Originals", undated; ID: 268.0048; 222237 (Box 10, Media ID: 268.0048)
  - "Originals: Tape Given to Bryan Ferry", 1975; ID: 268.0090; 222347 (Box 10, Media ID: 268.0090)
  - "Refridgerator - Live at Max's", May 28 1980; ID: 268.0049; 222240 (Box 10, Media ID: 268.0049)
  - "The Rok Band Demo & Howard Stern", undated; ID: 268.0050; 222238 (Box 10, Media ID: 268.0050)
  - "Suzy Greengras & The Rok Band in Concert at Chapter Arts Center, Wales", August 18, 1977; ID: 268.0051; 222239 (Box 10, Media ID: 268.0051)
  - "Science - 13 Songs" [Empty Audio Cassette Case], 1977; ID: 268.0052; 222241 (Box 10, Media ID: 268.0052)
  - "Science", undated; ID: 258.0053; 222242 (Box 10, Media ID: 258.0053)
  - "Science Demo Master", undated; ID: 268.0054; 222243 (Box 10, Media ID: 268.0054)
  - "Science Demo (Mixed Down)", 1980; ID: 268.0055; 222244 (Box 10, Media ID: 268.0055)
  - "Science: The Ancient History; The First Science Demo", 1979; ID: 268.0056; 222245 (Box 10, Media ID: 268.0056)
  - "Science: Final Mix I", 1980; ID: 268.0057; 222246 (Box 10, Media ID: 268.0057)
  - "Science: Final Mix II", 1980; ID: 268.0058; 222248 (Box 10, Media ID: 268.0058)
  - "Science at Max's", March 19, 1980; ID: 268.0059; 222249 (Box 10, Media ID: 268.0059)
  - "Science Live at Max's", undated; ID: 268.0060; 222250 (Box 10, Media ID: 268.0060)
  - "Science Live at Max's (Black Label)", undated; ID: 268.0061; 222251 (Box 10, Media ID: 268.0061)
  - "Science Live Demo", undated; ID: 268.0062; 222252 (Box 10, Media ID: 268.0062)
  - "Science at Max's with Von LMO", undated; ID: 268.0063; 222253 (Box 10, Media ID: 268.0063)
  - "Science Max's LP Remastered", undated; ID: 268.0064; 222254 (Box 10, Media ID: 268.0064)
  - "Science - Live Demo", 1985; ID: 268.0084; 222307 (Box 10, Media ID: 268.0084)
  - "Science LP - Ruff Mix", 1978; ID: 268.0065; 222255 (Box 10, Media ID: 268.0065)
  - "Science LP - Ruff Mix", undated; ID: 268.0066; 222256 (Box 10, Media ID: 268.0066)
  - "Science: Instrumental Final Mix", undated; ID: 268.0067; 222257 (Box 10, Media ID: 268.0067)
  - "Science at Max's / Rehearsal at Scance's", undated; ID: 268.0068; 222258 (Box 10, Media ID: 268.0068)
  - "Science Rehearsal - Wooster Street Studio", May 15, 1984; ID: 268.0069; 222259 (Box 10, Media ID: 268.0069)
  - "Science Rehearsal at Legal Tender Studios", undated; ID: 268.0070; 222260 (Box 10, Media ID: 268.0070)
  - "Science Rehearsal at Scance's with Joe Montag on Synth", undated; ID: 268.0071; 222261 (Box 10, Media ID: 268.0071)
  - "Science Rehearsal at Robert's", October 30, 1983; ID: 268.0072; 222262 (Box 10, Media ID: 268.0072)
  - "Science Rehearsal Including Darker Day Away", undated; ID: 268.0073; 222263 (Box 10, Media ID: 268.0073)
  - "Science Rehearsal at Scance's with Joe Montage on Synth (1st Half)", undated; ID: 268.0074; 222264 (Box 10, Media ID: 268.0074)
  - "Science Rehearsal at Moogtown", undated; ID: 268.0075; 222265 (Box 10, Media ID: 268.0075)
  - "Scramble It" by SE Greengras, 1980; ID: 268.0076; 222299 (Box 10, Media ID: 268.0076)
  - "Son of Science", undated; ID: 268.0077; 222300 (Box 10, Media ID: 268.0077)
  - "Story of Dictation, Mike 1", undated; ID: 268.0078; 222301 (Box 10, Media ID: 268.0078)
  - "Suzy & Lenny Lopate on Air Phone-In", undated; ID: 268.0079; 222302 (Box 10, Media ID: 268.0079)
  - "Suzy Greengras Live at WBAI", 1974; ID: 268.0080; 222303 (Box 10, Media ID: 268.0080)
  - "Suzy Greengras - Unstuck in Time", undated; ID: 268.0081; 222304 (Box 10, Media ID: 268.0081)
  - "Suzy on Guitar - The Fat Lady of Limbourg", undated; ID: 268.0082; 222305 (Box 10, Media ID: 268.0082)
  - "Tim & Suzy Live", undated; ID: 268.0089; 222346 (Box 10, Media ID: 268.0089)
  - "Von LMO at Max's", July 4, 1981; ID: 268.0083; 222306 (Box 10, Media ID: 268.0083)
  - "Von LMO: Future Language LP", 1981; ID: 268.0085; 222308 (Box 10, Media ID: 268.0085)
  - "Von LMO International Shortwave Pirate Broadcast", August 15, 1980; ID: 268.0086; 222309 (Box 10, Media ID: 268.0086)
  - "Von LMO Rehearsal", July 14, 1992; ID: 268.0087; 222337 (Box 10, Media ID: 268.0087)
  - "Winter Heart, Carey, New Androgyny Riff", undated; ID: 268.0088; 222338 (Box 10, Media ID: 268.0088)
- Series VII: Data Storage, 220146
  Born-digital materials have not been preserved and are not currently available to researchers.
  - "Vol I: Johnny Science", undated; 222522 (Box 11, Disk ID: 268.3.0001)
    Format: Memorex IBM 2SHD
    Capacity: 1.44MB
  - "Vol II: Johnny Science", undated; 222523 (Box 11, Disk ID: 268.3.0002)
  - "Drag King Club - Promo Stuff", undated; 222524 (Box 11, Disk ID: 268.3.0003)
  - "IBM = AOL Chat Room 'BelAmi27,' Max's Letter", undated; 222525 (Box 11, Disk ID: 268.3.0004)
    Format: Maxell MF 2HD
    Capacity: [unknown]
  - "Johnny", undated; 222526 (Box 11, Disk ID: 268.3.0005)
  - "Johnny Science 3", undated; 222527 (Box 11, Disk ID: 268.3.0006)
    Format: MAC100 Iomega
    Capacity: 100 MB
  - "Johnny Science Z2", undated; 222528 (Box 11, Disk ID: 268.3.0007)
  - "That Show/Johnny Science CG Credits #1", undated; 222529 (Box 11, Disk ID: 268.3.0008)
  - [Mixed Personal Photography], 01/16/2007; 222530 (Box 11, Disk ID: 268.3.0009)
    Format: CD
- Series VIII: Comic Books, 1964-1997
  - Amazing Spiderman, The, May 1965 (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - Amazing Spiderman, The, Dec. 1968 (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - Battlefield Action, Aug. 1964 (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - Boris Karloff Tales of Mystery, Jan. 1964 (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - Brave and the Bold Presents 3 Battle Stars, The, Feb./Mar. 1964 (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - Car 54, Where Are You?, Jan.-Mar. 1965 (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - Dracual Lives, July 1965 (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - Fightin': Air Force, Sept. 1964 (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - Fightin': Navy, Oct. 1964 (Box 13, Folder 9)
  - Haunted Tank, The, Aug./Sept.1965 (Box 13, Folder 10)
  - I... Vampire! Starring in the House of Mystery, Sept. 1982 (Box 13, Folder 11)
  - Man From U.N.C.L.E., The, Nov. 1966 (Box 13, Folder 12)
  - Sgt. Fury and his Howling Commandos, Mar. 1964 (Box 13, Folder 13)
  - Sgt. Fury and his Howling Commandos, Nov. 1964 (Box 13, Folder 14)
  - Sgt. Fury and his Howling Commandos, Jan. 1971 (Box 13, Folder 15)
  - Sgt. Rock's Easy Co. in Our Army at War, Mar. 1962 (Box 13, Folder 16)
  - Sgt. Rock's Easy Co. in Our Army at War, Mar. 1963 (Box 13, Folder 17)
  - Sgt. Rock's Easy Co. in Our Army at War, Oct. 1963 (Box 13, Folder 18)
  - Sgt. Rock's Easy Co. in Our Army at War, Sept. 1964 (Box 13, Folder 19)
  - Sgt. Rock's Easy Co. in Our Army at War, Oct. 1964 (Box 13, Folder 20)
  - Sgt. Rock's Easy Co. in Our Army at War, July 1965 (Box 13, Folder 21)
  - Trinity Angels, Nov. 1997 (Box 13, Folder 22)
  - The Twilight Zone, Oct. 1967 (Box 13, Folder 23)
  - War Heroes, Oct. 1964 (Box 13, Folder 24)
  - War Stories Combat that Incredible Story of D-Day Invasion at Normandy, Oct. 1972 (Box 13, Folder 25)
- OVERSIZE Series I: Projects, 220154
  - The Eulenspiegel Society: Pro-me-thee-us - A Sexual Minorities Report - Volume 1, Issue 1 [Newspaper], 1973; 221735 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - The Eulenspiegel Society: Pro-me-thee-us - A Sexual Minorities Report - Special Introductory Issue [Newspaper], 1973; 221736 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - "The Eyes of Age" by Johnny Science, undated; 221737 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - F2M Fraternity: Drag King Club [Administrative File], c1994; 221738 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - F2M Fraternity: Drag King Club Balls [Posters], [no year]; 221739 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - F2M Fraternity: Drag King Club - Club Casanova [Posters], undated; 221789 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - F2M Fraternity: Drag King Club - "Diane Torre's Drag Kings & Subjects" [Poster], February 1995; 221790 (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - F2M Fraternity: Drag King Club - "Life on Mars, An Alternative Cabaret" [Posters], [no year]; 221791 (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - "It's the Cut, Dr. Freud: Why One Woman Loves Men's Clothes" by Ingrid Sischy, 09/13/1992; 221793 (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Jovian Gentlemen: 1997 Calendars, 221794 (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - [Leather: Oversize Images], various; 221795 (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - [LBGT: Events Posters], 1991 - 1998; 221798 (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - "The Master Has a Big Bone For His Dog" [Illustration by Johnny Science], 08/16/1974; 221799 (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - National Leather Association: 1995 Calendars, March - June 1995; 221801 (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - National Leather Association: "Fundamentals of Flagellation" [Posters], 04/29/1996; 221802 (Box 7, Folder 15)
  - National Leather Association International: The Link - Living in Leather XI [Newsletter], July 1996; 221803 (Box 7, Folder 16)
  - The Oracle: Dwight Morrow High School - Volume 69, Number 3 [Newsletter], October 20, 1972; 221804 (Box 7, Folder 17)
  - [Oversize Loose Images], undated; 221805 (Box 7, Folder 18)
  - Paper Tiger - Volume 2, Number 2 [Newsletter], November 1973; 221808 (Box 7, Folder 19)
  - Sage: United Community for the Aging [Newsletters], June - July 1992; 221809 (Box 7, Folder 20)
  - Tom of Finland Boots Poster, 1981; 221810 (Box 7, Folder 21)
  - Tom of Finland "One Way" Poster, 1989; 231283 (Box 7, Folder 22)
- OVERSIZE Series IV: Objects, 222047
  - "Priapus Incarnate" by Dan Austen [Illustration on Wood], June 1994; 221998 (Box 8, Object ID: 268.2.0004)
  - [Black Phallic Pillow], undated; 222000 (Box 8, Object ID: 268.2.0005)
  - Jovian Gentlemen Donation Tin, undated; 222003 (Box 8, Object ID: 268.2.0006)
  - Jovian Gentlemen Umbrella, undated; 222004 (Box 8, Object ID: 268.2.0007)
  - Leather jacket and cap, undated; 262743 (Box 12)